Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ movindugunarathna (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Leadership

Communication

Public Speaking

Certifications

Java SE 11 Programmer II: Streams & Pipelines

Agile Fundamentals: Stakeholders, Success Criteria, Users, and the Agile Team

Working with Spring Data JPA: Derived Query Methods

Java Spring Cloud: Securing Microservices

JavaScript: Prototypes

Movindu Thiumila Gunarathna

Undergraduate | Associate Software Engineer | MERN Stack Western Province, Sri Lanka

Summary

Ambitious undergraduate student in the Software Development field, currently working as an Associate Software Engineer. Whose expertise lies in Javascript, Java and Kotlin. Additionally, has a keen interest in working with frameworks such as React, Express and Angular.

I believe that my commitment to leadership and ability to seamlessly collaborate within a team is what truly distinguishes me. Being a fast learner with strong problem-solving and creativity skills, I am poised to be a highly valuable asset in this journey.

Experience

HCLTech

1 year 9 months

Associate Software Engineer May 2023 - Present (5 months) Sri Lanka

Software Engineer Intern January 2022 - May 2023 (1 year 5 months) Sri Lanka

Education

Ananda College

Physical Sciences · (2012 - 2020)

University of Westminster
BEng(Hons) Software Engineering (2021)

Aquinas College of Higher Studies

Diploma in English Language and Literature (2018 - 2018)